# JC Guzman

## Computer Technician

Self-motivated Computer Technician with background in email account and connectivity set up for large organizations. Determined employee with over 13 years of system upgrade and network component installation experience. Highly knowledgeable in demonstrating software features to employees.

## **Work History**

#### 2021-04 -Current

## Computer Technician

Hayward Unified School District, Hayward, CA

- Responded to support requests from end users and patiently walked individuals through basic troubleshooting tasks.
- Linked computers to network and peripheral equipment, including printers and scanners.
- Backed up company data on regular basis, successfully recovering critical information after malware attacks.
- Configured hardware, devices and software to set up work stations for employees.
- Supported training departments and schools by accurately fixing hardware and software issues affecting computers and language labs.

#### 2020-01 -2021-04

#### **Enterprise Account Manager**

Comcast Business, San Jose, CA

- Asked appropriate questions to identify prospects' needs and pinpoint solutions for best fit.
- Marketed and sold solutions and services to stakeholders across multiple levels of organization.
- Worked with service and project management departments to provide total support to clients.
- Developed creative solutions to meet individual client needs.
- Demonstrated products, responded to questions, redirected concerns and overcame objections to

#### Contact

#### **Address**

San Leandro, CA, 94578

#### **Phone**

(510) 387-4710

#### E-mail

jcguz7@gmail.com

#### **WWW**

https://zety.com/profile/jc-guzman/317

#### **Skills**

Help desk support



Desktop and laptop installations



Technical Support



Email account set up



Security best practices



Technical Analysis



Network component

close sales.

 Enhanced success of advertising strategies by boosting engagement through social media and other digital marketing approaches.

## Excellent

#### 2017-10 - Sales Representative/ Kitchen Hood 2021-01 Technician

TLC Cleaning, Bay Area, CA

- Acquire and maintain commercial restaurant accounts.
- Negotiate bids on restaurant kitchen hoods for monthly cleaning.
- B2B door sales acquiring new accounts to add to existing portfolio.
- Manage monthly schedule for service appointments.
- Assist contractors in cleaning restaurant hoods.
- Collect and manage account payments.

## 2018-06 - Route Sales Driver

2019-04

2017-01

Fieldwork Brewing, Berkeley, CA

- Establish and maintain effective customer relationships to initiate and maximize sales in retail restaurants.
- Acquire and maintain restaurant accounts.
- Manage weekly route schedule.
- Utilize logistics order managing tools/peripherals.

## 2013-07 - Xfinity Sales Professional

Comcast Cable, San Francisco, CA

- Build and maintain relationships with realtors, property managers and local community centers.
- Generate new sales and leads by penetrating assigned turf.
- D2D sales presenting Comcast services to potential and existing customers.
- Met with existing customers and prospects to discuss business needs and recommend optimal solutions.
- Developed and delivered engaging sales presentations to convey product benefits.

## 2013-09 - IT Manager

2015-09 Acme Anything INC/Found On Piedmont, Oakland, CA

## **Education**

#### AA: Liberal Arts

Chabot College - Hayward, CA

## Diploma

Arroyo High School - San Lorenzo, CA

## **Comptia A+ Courses**

Stride Center - Oakland,CA